A Guide to the Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 1 FA078
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Agricultural Development Council photographs, 1959-1971; 1032
  - Rural Dynamics Project - Indonesia (Box 13, Folder 175)
  - Silliman University, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 176)